questionsOne = [
    {
        "Question":"1. Which one is NOT a legal variable name?",

        "choices": [
            "my-var",
            "-myvar",
            "Myvar",
            "my_var",
        ],
        "Answer": "-myvar",
    },
    {
        "Question":"2. How do you create a variable with the numeric value 5",
        "choices": [
            "x = int(5)",
            "x = 5",
            "Both the other answer are correct",
            "All of them are wrong",
        ],
        "Answer": "Both the answer are correctr",
    },
    {
        "Question":"3. What is the correct file extension for Python files?",
        "choices": [
            ".pyth",
            ".pt",
            ".pyt",
            ".py",
        ],
        "Answer": ".py",
    },
    {
        "Question":"4. How do you create a variable with the floating number 2.8?",
        "choices": [
                "x = 2.8",
                "x = float(2.8)",
                "x = 2.8(float)",
                "Both the other answer are correct",
        ],
        "Answer":"Both the other answer are correct",
    },
    {
        "Question":"5. What is the correct way to create a function in Python?",
        "choices": [
                "create myFunction()",
                "def myFunction()",
                "function myfunction()",
                "create Function()",
        ],
        "Answer": "def myFunction()",
    },
    {
        "Question":"6. In Python, 'Hello', is the same as 'Hello'",
        "choices": [
                "True",
                "False",
                "None",
                "Undefined"
        ],
        "Answer": "True",
    },
    {
        "Question":"7. What is a correct syntax to return the first character in a string?",
        "choices": [
                'x = sub("Hello", 0,1)',
                "x = 'Hello'.sub(0,1)",
                "x = 'Hello'[0]",
                "x = 'Hello'.sub[0]",
        ],
        "Answer": "x = 'Hello'[0]",
    },
    {
        "Question":"8. Which method can be used to replace parts of a string?",
        "choices": [
                'replace()',
                "replaceString()",
                "repl()",
                "switch()",
        ],
        "Answer": "repl()",
    },
    {
        "Question":"9. Which operator is used to multiply numbers?",
        "choices": [
                'x',
                "#",
                "%",
                "*",
        ],
        "Answer": "*",
    },
    {
        "Question":"10. Which operator can be used to compare two values?",
        "choices": [
                '><',
                "<>",
                "=",
                "==",
        ],
        "Answer": "==",
    },
]
